Who was the first to find him?
Could they please answer
a few questions for us?
Who's the culprit?
Are there any suspects?
Is there any connection between this and
the annihilation of the Franky house?
What's the condition?
Could you give us a statement, please?
Hey, did you hear about what happened
at the shipbuilding island last night?
Is it true? Did he die?
Franky did this.
I just know it.
You let someone like that run around
free and this is what happened.
Well,
it might have been those
pirates who've been
hanging around the
shipyards the past few days.
So this is where you've been.
We went through all the trouble of
renting a room and no one's using it.
I guess nobody could sleep, huh?
And where's Luffy?
Over there.
So where were you?
I kept lookout around
the rocky Cape all night.
I wanted to be there in
case Robin came back.
Oh,
she never said
anything about leaving.
I wonder where she went?
I think I'll try looking
around for her in town today.
Do you think we're going to find her?
Who knows?
It's not like I have any place
specific in mind to check out.
I just feel certain that
she's still here somewhere.
If anything should happen, we should
use this inn as our meet-up point.
I want to help.
I'm going to come too.
All right then come on Nami what's
wrong it's awful the whole city's talking
about it Luffy listen to me last night
something terrible happened to Iceberg
What Iceberg was shot in his home stop
screwing around is this some kind of
Joke no joke is he alive who would do
such a thing everyone loves him he's
alive.
Calm down, Polly.
Listen to me for a second. Okay?
He was discovered in his room
early this morning, lying
in a pool of his own blood.
Like I said, he's alive, but he's
been unconscious since he was found.
You need to come to the
main office immediately.
Lulu, where's Polly?
I just called him.
He'll be here soon. Good.
Reporters are all over
the place.
It's mass hysteria out there.
We are the ones who'd like
to know what happened.
The office has been torn apart, but
there's no trace of anything being stolen.
No money,
no valuables, nothing.
If this wasn't a robbery, then the
question is, who would try to kill
Iceberg and why?
At any rate, we're in big trouble here.
The city's in total panic.
If anything should happen to Iceberg,
then it's not only the end
for the Galley-La Company,
but the entire city of Water 7 as well.
Doctor, please.
What is his condition?
He was shot two times in the front,
and another three from behind.
I have no idea what happened in that
room last night, but it was brutal.
According to forensics,
there's no sign of the
locks being picked to
his office or anywhere
else in the building.
The incident occurred in a
room no one could have entered.
The only thing out of place they found was
a mask you can buy just about anywhere.
Ice pops from the shipyard?
Yes, I've heard he's still unconscious.
I thought everybody in this
entire city loved that guy.
Why him?
Who are you talking about?
He's the nice man that helped
us out so much yesterday.
The president of the shipbuilding
company as well as the mayor of Water 7.
Sounds like an important guy.
Yeah, it's pretty much the worst thing
that could have happened to this town.
I'll go check on him.
On that
note,
let's go look for Robin.
Come on, Chopper?
What about you?
Well, I think I'll just wait a
while, see how things turn out.
Extra, extra, read all about it!
Iceberg, our beloved mayor
and the hero of Water 7,
has fallen victim to the
hands of an assassin!
This is an urgent news
report covering the incident!
This is terrible.
Is Iceberg okay?
How awful.
Who would do such a thing?
Only pirates would pull a vicious
attack like that out of nowhere.
No doubt about it.
I'd like to get my hands
on the ones that did it.
There were a bunch of pirates
rampaging through Doc 1 just yesterday.
You mean the Mikazuki gang?
I know it sounds crazy, but I think
the government did this. What?
What are you saying?
I'm talking about Corgi.
Every time he comes to talk with
Iceberg, he gets rejected and leaves.
I'm telling you, Franky did it!
I don't really know what he's
trying to speak with him about,
but he must have done this out of spite.
I'd keep that theory to myself.
If you openly blame the world
government, it won't be taken lightly.
Is this diabolical criminal's
goal to gain wealth or power?
Who is this nameless assassin
that disappeared without a trace?
Who in the hell did this?
I'm not gonna let him get away with it!
Thank you for writing this feature.
Next stop, Station at War 7.
Arighting momentarily.
Holy!
A word, please.
Can we get a comment about this incident?
What were you told before you came here?
Shut up, all of you.
Get the hell out of my way.
Tell us, what explanation were
you given by your company?
Polly, please, a comment.
I don't have time for this crap.
Get out of here.
Are you aware of any incident that can
cause someone to target Iceberg's life?
Anything at all?
There must be something.
Any altercations with pirates?
Didn't you idiots hear me?
Get out of here!
So I guess the rumors are true he was
attacked yeah so if we go to the shipyard it's
likely We won't be able to meet with him
then let's just go to his house I believe
he lives inside The main office kiwi mozu
am am I asleep is this a dream this is
no dream without a doubt this is was the
very spot where the Franky house stood.
But something like this
happening just seems so extreme.
What the hell is going on?
Who would be stupid enough to
do something like this to my
house hold on I know who damn
you Straw Hat Luffy so this
is your payback for us stealing
your 200 million berries
how dare you treat my faithful
men this way it's so heartless
Unforgivable
Franky, bro! You came back! Franky!
You guys are alright?
What a relief.
Thank goodness.
It was terrible.
Those pirates are completely insane.
Listen, we've been keeping track
of what the Straw Hats are up to.
We know there's no way you're
gonna let them get away with this!
Where are they now?
It's all going to an end.
After that, they headed over
to the shipbuilding island.
It's Doc 1.
They were there yesterday.
I bet that's where they're going.
Is that so?
All right, then.
Straw Hat Luffy.
When I find you, I'm
going to rip you apart.
Whoa! Whoa!
Granny! Granny!
The wind is blowing like crazy!
Crazy wind!
Enough already. Keep it down.
The southern wind, huh?
Must be current.
The waves are getting rough, too.
Well, if this keeps up, the sea
train won't be able to run tonight.
Timmy, Conve, get ready.
We're going back to the island.
Okay.
Aqua Laguna is coming.
Your attention please.
This is the Water 7
Weather Forecasting Center.
As of now,
an Aqua Laguna severe weather warning has
just been issued for the entire island.
its arrival time is estimated to be
sometime between midnight and 12 30.
oh yeah i guess it Is about
that time I've been preoccupied
with what happened to iceberg
hey aqua laguna is coming?
Make sure everybody
knows about the warning
all right no more work
for today what'd he say?
Aqua Laguna.
Oh, excuse me.
What was that broadcast about just now?
What do you mean?
Everybody knows what...
Oh, wait, are you a visitor here?
Sorry, you've come sightseeing
at a really bad time.
Aqua Laguna is an annual storm.
It's about to pass through here.
A storm, huh?
A big one.
You're going to need to
evacuate to higher ground.
This entire city will be underwater soon.
Underwater? Really?
Don't worry.
It's not going to happen
right this second.
According to the forecast, it'll
arrive sometime around midnight.
The locals have gotten used
to it, and you'll remember.
See ya! Later.
Hmm, the whole town will be...
Wait, it's going to sink?
Yeah, apparently so.
We need to find Robin and Quick.
Come on.
Right.
Can't you tell us anything?
Hey, Iceberg!
What happened here?
What's going on?
I can't go that way, man.
We're never gonna find out what's going on
unless we find some
way to get to ice pops.
Um, excuse me.
Can you tell me where the
entrance of the main office is?
Yeah, it's head dock one.
But I don't think you're
gonna have any luck
getting in with everything
that happened here.
They're only allowing authorized
personnel to get through.
You're not alone.
Everyone wants in.
We're all so worried about him.
I see.
Thank you.
Look at all those people.
What's all the commotion about?
Well, the bigger the audience,
the better, I always say.
No!
Don't tell me!
It's that rhythm! What? Why
now? Hey, guys! Question!
Did you just say my name?
No, we didn't! Just go away!
Where is he?
Where's he coming from?
I don't see him!
Wait, he's up there!
Oh, no! Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Come on, everybody!
No need to be shy!
Say my name!
We don't want to! Get lost!
You're the one who attacked
Iceberg, aren't you?
Yeah, he has to be!
Just leave!
Get the hell out of here!
Hang that gunfight, not that punk!
What a bunch of noisy flies.
I'm one of seven's number one super guy the
face of the underworld and you know why!
I'm the man with the
plan the power and fame
and people everywhere
call out my name wow?
Mm!
Franky!
Come out and show yourself, Straw Hat!
Stop being such a pansy!
Get out here and fight me already!
I don't know how that
weirdo figured out my name.
I've never seen him before in my life!
Didn't you hear what those people said?
I think that guy might be Franky!
Then we found him!
He's the one who beat up Usopp!
This money belongs to us now, understand?
No!
Give it back!
It wasn't for him!
Luffy!
Hey!
Bikini guy!
Hold on a sec!
That's me!
I'm Straw Hat!
There's still no information?
What's going on?
Everyone?
So what's the word?
You may enter, but try to keep your
voices down, please. Then he...
he's okay?
His injuries are still serious, but Mr.
Iceberg has finally
regained consciousness.
That's great news!
Come on, let's see how he's doing.
You're okay!
Well, I've been better, I suppose.
All things considered,
you're pretty lucky.
Anyway, you just focus on getting better.
In the meantime, you can count on us
to take care of the shipyard, okay?
Yes, of course.
Now I need to talk to you about the
people who broke into my room last night.
Uh, yeah.
Well, that's still under
investigation, I'm afraid.
No, I remember them. Huh?
There were two.
One of them was a large man who was
wearing a mask, and the other was a woman.
Tall, with long black hair.
I could never forget those eyes.
It has to be her.
I can't believe what I just heard. Mr.
Iceberg's awake, everyone!
It looks like our mayor's gonna be okay!
Is that true? All right!
I knew he'd make it! Yes!
So you're Luffy, huh?
Didn't expect you to look so shrimpy.
I got a bone to pick with you, kid.
It seems you and your
gang had a little party at
my place while I was gone
when I came home now?
What did I see my house
is up to shreds and my
gang was on its knees and
it's all thanks to Luffy!
I'll make this as plain as can be when you
mess with my voice you mess with Franky!
I'd hate to be you right
now cuz I'm on one hell
of a roll this week and
ain't nobody gonna stop me!
Now you can cry if you
like but either way!
I'm gonna pound you so hard even your own
mother won't recognize you when I'm done.
Shut up! Huh?
You jerk!
Give us our 200 million berries
back already! You hear me?
Huh?
You want your money back, you say?
Well, that's a damn shame,
because I'm afraid I spent it all!
You pirates are all a
bunch of sore losers.
Don't act all high and mighty when you
probably just stole the
money from someone else.
The money doesn't matter.
Maybe not to you, but it does to me.
All I care about now is getting revenge,
So money or no money,
I'm gonna make you pay!
You're stealing my lines, you bastard!
Are you trying to make me mad?
Whatever!
Just come down here and fight!
Uh-oh!
Everybody get out of the way!
Frankie's going on a rampage! Come away!
Is he holding his breath or something?
Weird.
He just spit fire!
Yeah, I can see that much, but how?
Oh? You scared?
Having second thoughts?
Careful!
If he can do that, he might
have Devil Fruit powers!
Okay, but that doesn't really help!
If that guy did eat a Devil Fruit, he
wouldn't just jump in the water for no reason.
Would he?
Maybe nobody told him that if
you tried to swim, you'd die.
That'd be pretty pathetic,
but at least it would save us the
trouble of fighting that weirdo.
I guess he can't swim!
Lucky didn't drown, huh?
I didn't eat no Devil Fruit.
You think I'm crazy?
Huh?
Doesn't matter to me!
Can't surprise me.
I heard about that little power of yours.
Stronger!
What?
Oh, man.
Lupi!
Hey!
Are you okay?
If you don't have Devil Fruit
powers, then what are you?
Huh?
You poor saps don't know
anything now, do you?
All right, then.
I'll humor you.
I'm just a normal guy
with some extra parts.
A cyborg, you might say.
One of the Straw Hats did this?
Sure about that?
Of all people? Yes.
And my personal investigation
led to the same result.
To make sure I had Lucy, contact the
government to confirm her identity and bounty.
Yes.
They said she's a notorious criminal, so
it's no surprise that she'd do something.
Catastrophe to our boss! Cuckoo!
And our next course of
action is crystal clear.
We gotta find those rapscallions
and show them what's what.
What in the hell were they thinking?
Don't tell me they're pissed off
because we wouldn't fix their ship.
I wonder that myself.
But regardless of what
their motivations might be,
the bottom line is that they're the
culprits and they need to be dealt with.
In other words,
we should just capture the
Straw Hats and interrogate them
ourselves instead of wasting time
trying to figure this crap out.
None of this makes sense to me,
but anyone who messes with
Galley-La is gonna have hell to pay.
Hey! There's trouble!
Shut up, Tile Stone!
You're way the hell too loud!
You fools!
You're just as loud as he is!
Oh!
I didn't know you were up already, Mr.
Iceberg! That's great!
He may be awake, but that doesn't
mean you should scream his ears off.
Take it down a notch or two, okay?
I'm sorry!
I can't help it! I swear!
Oh, I almost forgot!
I had a turn or something!
Fine, but stay outside.
You can tell me from over there.
We got trouble with that Straw Hat guy!
I don't know what happened,
but he got in a big fight with Franky and
they're both wrecking up the shipyard.
If we don't stop them,
who knows what they'll do?
Straw Hat again?
But at least we know where to find him.
He's got some nerve.
I'll teach that punk to
show his face on our turf.
Now you can finally have
a bit of peace and quiet.
Let them take care of Straw Hat.
I'll be watching over you in the meantime.
So there's no need to worry.
Come, come.
Watch out, it's coming down!
It turns to the ship.
Stop it, go fight somewhere else.
Ah!
Luffy!
Tear him to pieces and then
they can put some pants on!
Hey, bro.
You gotta put on a good show.
You're a lot tougher
than I thought you'd be.
But I'm still gonna beat you, bikini guy!
If you say so,
Now it's gonna take a long-ass time
with those weenie attacks of yours.
Weapons left!
Go, go!
I can't see.
It seems like they both got hit.
No, look who it is.
Who just punched me?
This is too easy.
If you knew what was good for you, you
would have skipped town a long time ago.
You're in for it now.
Gally-la.
Great, that's just what I need.
All right, the guys from
Doc Ward finally made it.
Lock those loosers up
and throw away the key.
Whoo!
All right, the four men will
take care of these guys.
That was close.
If they didn't show up, the whole
shipyard was gonna get totaled.
Wow, lucky break.
Finally, someone can put
a stop to this nonsense.
I bet they hate Franky, too.
I'd butt out of this if I were you.
Once these fists start
rocking and rolling,
they don't discriminate between
pirates and shipwrights.
And that goes for other
people's property, too.
Surely you don't expect us
to stand here gobsmacked
while you wreck our entire shipyard.
I'm warning you, Franky!
If you don't pay for these repairs
and berries, you'll pay in blood!
All right, Tile Stone, calm down.
We can take care of
Franky some other time.
We've got more important
business to deal with right now.
Yeah, I'm looking at you, Straw Hat.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
I don't know if you're brave or
stupid, but either way, you're dead.
Wait, what?
We just came here because we
heard the news about Ice Pops.
Wasn't enough to wreck my
house and beat up my boys, huh?
What's wrong?
Don't feel like a man unless you're
pounding the crap out of ship rights, too?
I know the puberty can make
you do some really crazy stuff,
but wow I don't even know what's going on?
So stop making fun of me play innocent
all you like I won't go easy on you!
Romance and Half-Nob!
Don't breathe.
Air drive!
Dammit, just go away!
I told you shipwrights to
stay out of this, didn't I?
I'm the one who owes this
guy a beating, not you!
Go Galilass!
Show them what you're made of!
There's no way they can beat the
top five shipwrights in the city!
What?
Why are the shipwrights
fighting against us, too?
Makes me itchy.
What are you doing?
I don't have any reason to fight you guys!
Just hold on!
Look at that.
He's got Devil Fruit power.
Hey, stupid, are you even listening?
How many times do I
have to tell you bozos?
For the last time.
Straw Hat is mine, dammit!
Sorry, Franky, but we don't have
time for your shenanigans today.
Get the hell out of my
way, you flying monkey!
You're the one who's in the way!
Oh, yeah!
That's our tile stone!
He's even stronger than usual today!
Cuckoo! Cuckoo! Cuckoo! Cuckoo!
Hey, stop it!
Damn, you guys are strong!
But I still don't know why we're fighting!
Straw Hat, I think we're the ones who
deserve an explanation here, not you.
Someone broke into
Iceberg's house last night.
Shot him twice in the front and three
times in the back before they left.
They were from your crew.
That can't be!
None of us would do that!
I'm never gonna settle this, am I?
That was Nico Robin.
There's not a single doubt in my mind.
But was that masked man one
of the Straw Hats as well?
And why did they attack
me in the first place?
Surely it wasn't about their ship.
No, they must have been
aiming to steal something.
But seeing as they left empty-handed, I
have a good idea what they were looking for.
The question is, if they were
working with the government,
or if they want it for themselves.
Straw Hat Luffy.
This just in!
Breaking news!
Iceberg has already identified the
culprits from the break-in last night!
What?
Is that true?
Spread the word through the city
and we'll capture them ourselves!
We can't let those criminals
leave Water 7! Who did it?
Show no mercy to the monsters
who attacked our mayor!
Capture the Straw Hat Pirates
no matter what it takes!
Iceberg was shot?
That's news to me.
Dad, can't be! We.
No way!
We didn't shoot Ice Pops.
That's just crazy!
There were two people who broke
into his room and attacked him.
He may have been hurt.
But that doesn't mean he didn't
get a good look at him first.
One of them was a big guy with a mask on.
The other was a tall
woman with black hair.
Iceberg told us he recognized her and the
government confirmed she's
a member of your crew.
The archaeologist, Nico Robin.
You're lying!
I won't ask you why.
Maybe your crew came to Water
7 on a mission to kill Iceberg.
Or maybe you really did
want your ship repaired
and attacked him on a whim
after we turned you down.
I don't know how you pirates
think, and I don't care.
Point is, you tried to kill my boss,
and now I'm gonna have to take you down.
So he's one of the culprits?
Tie him up, Polly!
Don't let that pirate go!
This is bad.
So he got shot five times,
but Iceberg's still alive?
Don't look so surprised.
That guy's as tough as nails.
But if they tried it once,
then these scumbags might try to go
after Iceberg a second time, too.
So we're gonna settle this now.
Dead or alive, the world
government doesn't care either way.
This is what it means to
have a bounty on your head.
Therefore, you can't complain, no
matter how terrible your fate may be.
You've broken the law, and now the
law has turned its back on you.
That's right.
We chose to live this way.
We're all outlaws, but I don't care.
You're wrong!
If you knew Robin, you wouldn't say that!
Take that back!
Luffy, let me talk to Ice Pops.
This has to be a mistake.
There's no way it was Robin.
We'd be fools to let
you anywhere near him.
Criminals have no right to make demands.
He's right!
Shut up the conference!
Those bastards can't get
away with shooting our hero!
Send him to the gallows!
Hey, wait!
Just calm down! Hold on!
What?
You can't fool me, Missy!
I saw you with that Straw Hat guy!
I bet you're one of the
criminals, aren't ya?
Really? Yeah!
She was riding along with him
on a yagra when he got here!
We've got you now!
You're gonna get what you deserve!
Stop it! Let me go!
Nami!
Word of this is going
to spread like wildfire.
There's no place to run
and no place to hide.
It's the end of the road.
You pirates are going down.
Extra, extra, read all about it.
The Straw Hat Pirates were the
culprits in the attack against Mr.
Iceberg.
The Water Water newspaper
will purchase any information
related to their current
location or actions.
We know that the culprits
are still here on the island,
so be sure to stay on the lookout!
We must band together to hunt down the
Straw Hats and send them to the gallows!
Yeah!